export const mobiledata = [
    {
      question: 'What services does your company provide?',
      answer: ' We provide installation, repairs, maintenance, management, and verification services for homes and organizations. Our qualified artisans handle electrical, plumbing, smart home devices, security systems, HVAC systems, and more.'
    },
    {
        question: 'How can I trust the quality of your artisans?',
        answer: 'We take pride in our rigorous vetting process. Each artisan is carefully selected based on their qualifications, experience, and track record. We ensure they meet our high standards of professionalism and expertise.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Can I monitor and manage my facilities remotely?',
        answer: 'Absolutely! Our web app allows you to conveniently monitor and manage your facilities from anywhere. You can access real-time project reports, repair history, and facility health status, empowering you with valuable insights.'
      },
      {
        question: 'Can I customize a maintenance plan that suits my specific needs?',
        answer: 'Yes, you can subscribe to a customized maintenance plan. We understand that every facility has unique requirements, so we work closely with you to design a plan that aligns with your goals and ensures optimal facility performance.'
      },
      {
        question: 'How does the Internet of Things (IoT) benefit facility monitoring?',
        answer: 'By harnessing IoT technology, you can smartly monitor your facilities based on factors like power consumption and current dissipation. This data-driven approach allows you to make informed decisions, optimize efficiency, and identify potential issues in real-time.'
      },
      {
        question: 'How do I book your services?',
        answer: 'Booking our services is simple. You can visit our website and use our user-friendly web app to schedule appointments, select the services you need, and receive transparent pricing details. It is hassle-free and saves you time.'
      },
      {
        question: ' What if I need urgent repairs outside of regular business hours?',
        answer: 'We understand that emergencies can happen at any time. Our services are available round the clock, including weekends and holidays. Simply reach out to our customer support, and we will promptly assist you.'
      },
      {
        question: ' Do you offer compliance and verification services?',
        answer: ' Yes, we provide verification and compliance services. Our expert team conducts electrical safety checks, ensures plumbing compliance, performs fire safety inspections, conducts energy efficiency audits, and assesses code compliance.'
      },
    {
      question: 'How do you ensure data privacy and security?',
      answer: 'We prioritize the confidentiality and security of your data. Our web app utilizes industry-standard security measures to protect your information. We comply with data privacy regulations and take appropriate measures to safeguard your data.'
    },
    {
      question: 'What are the benefits of subscribing to a maintenance plan?',
      answer: 'Subscribing to a maintenance plan offers several benefits. It helps extend the lifespan of your facilities, reduces the likelihood of unexpected breakdowns, lowers maintenance costs over time, and ensures consistent performance and optimal efficiency.'
    }
  ];